Akinduro Temitope Akinwumi

43 Olorunsogo Road Ibadan,Oyo- State. ♦ (234)7063450431♦ akinduroakinwumi@gmail.com

Objective

An articulate and quick thinking young person who has a natural flare for being able to communicate and build relationships with potential clients. He is creative and willing to contribute ideas and professional opinion to any project. He is more than able to aid with promotional efforts, advertising campaigns and public relations initiatives. He is presently seeking for a suitable position with an exciting and ambitious company.

Profile -

Motivated, personable business professional and over 2 years successful track record of profitable small business ownership. Talent for quickly mastering technology. Diplomatic and tactful with professionals and non-professionals at all levels.

Flexible and versatile – able to maintain a sense of humor under pressure. Poised and competent with demonstrated ability to easily transcend cultural differences. Thrive in deadline-driven environments. Excellent team-building skills.

Skills Summary

- ◆ Project Management
- ◆ Report Preparation
- ◆ General Office Skills
- ◆ Marketing & Sales
- ◆ Computer Savvy
- ◆ Customer Service
- Research and analyse scientific infomation
- ◆ Professional Presentations

Scheduling

Professional Experience -

COMMUNICATION: REPORTS/PRESENTATIONS/TECHNOLOGY

- Prepare complex reports for Animal health and disease control personnels.
- Design and deliver series of relevant information for local businesses and associations.
- ◆ Communicate medical concepts to livestock farmers using layman's terms to facilitate understanding.
- Rapidly learn and master varied computer programs; recently Microsoft Office Suite.

CUSTOMER SERVICE/MARKETING/PROBLEM SOLVING

- Oversee front-office operations and provide impeccable customer service:
- Develop and implement strategic marketing plan for business:
 - □ Create special promotions, write/design print and outdoor advertising and coordinate all media buying.

Employment History -

EXCEL TUTORS – Ibadan, Oyo state.

Tutor, 2018 Till Present

VICTORY FARMS – Ibadan, Oyo state.

Farm manager, 2016 to 2018

FEDERAL CAPITAL TERRITORY ADMINISTRATION, – Abuja, FCT-Nigeria.

Veterinarian Assistant, 2015 to 2016

COMMUNITY BASED FARMING SCHEME, – Federal University of Agriculture, Abeokuta.

Farm Operator, 2012/2013 session.

-Akinduro Temitope Akinwumi

Page Two Available for Relocation

Education -

NEW HORIZONES COMPUTER LEARNING CENTERS – Nigeria, Online and Digital Marketing (CIMP)

UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN – Ibadan, Nigeria
M.Sc Biochemistry and Technology of Agricultural Products, 2017-2019 (In view)

EXFORD GLOBAL CONSULT LIMITED – Abuja-FCT, Nigeria Human Resources Management Certificate, 2016

FEDERAL UNIVERSITY OF AGRICULTURE— Abeokuta, Nigeria B.Agic Animal Science, 2014

Computer Skills —

- ◆ Microsoft Word
- ♦ Microsoft Excel
- ♦ Microsoft PowerPoint

References _____

Dr K.P. Dandam, Assistant Head, Animal Service, Agriculture and Rural Development Secretariat, Federal Capital Territory Administration,FCT-Abuja (09080009998).

Chief A.O. Akintola. Member, Full Gospel Business Men's Fellowship International (08023113574).